<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>bilbois</title>
      <link>https://bilbois.me</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on bilbois</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Main Quests</title>
    <link>https://bilbois.me/Main-Vibes/Main-Quests</link>
    <guid>https://bilbois.me/Main-Vibes/Main-Quests</guid>
    <description>questlog Stuff I want do and need to do :) Related: Side Quests and Grinding. Personal Change the Quartz logo to myeye.ico. Work on my Obsidian vault - one note a day? Finish all of my programming projects.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 14:24:22 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>DVSA Theory Test Results Review (Maicey)</title>
    <link>https://bilbois.me/Unorganised/DVSA-Theory-Test-Results-Review-(Maicey)</link>
    <guid>https://bilbois.me/Unorganised/DVSA-Theory-Test-Results-Review-(Maicey)</guid>
    <description>Multiple Choice Breakdown 1. Road and Traffic Signs (6 marks needed) Understanding road signs is crucial for safe driving. This includes recognizing regulatory signs, warning signs, and information signs.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 02:16:41 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>My CV</title>
    <link>https://bilbois.me/Unorganised/My-CV</link>
    <guid>https://bilbois.me/Unorganised/My-CV</guid>
    <description>William Fayers Motivated undergraduate seeking part-time retail position to gain customer service experience. Ready to apply strong communication skills and passion for helping others to enhance the shopping experience.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 16:34:45 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>CV Chat (WIP)</title>
    <link>https://bilbois.me/Auto-Generated/AI-Chats/CV-Chat-(WIP)</link>
    <guid>https://bilbois.me/Auto-Generated/AI-Chats/CV-Chat-(WIP)</guid>
    <description>user: Read my Brother CV and Mother CV. They’re older and more experienced than me, I’m still an undergraduate student without any formal work experience beyond being a self-employed tutor for the past few years alongside my studies.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 01:08:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Side Quests</title>
    <link>https://bilbois.me/Main-Vibes/Side-Quests</link>
    <guid>https://bilbois.me/Main-Vibes/Side-Quests</guid>
    <description>questlog Just stuff I want to do at some point, but don’t need to do right now :) Related: Main Quests and Grinding. Programming Create a programming portfolio on tamago.tech within the unkokaeru repo.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:39:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Brother CV</title>
    <link>https://bilbois.me/Unorganised/Brother-CV</link>
    <guid>https://bilbois.me/Unorganised/Brother-CV</guid>
    <description>cv Alexander Fayers Security-focused software engineer based in England Security Cleared Experienced Software Developer First Class Cyber Security Degree Open to relocation ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:21:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Mother CV</title>
    <link>https://bilbois.me/Unorganised/Mother-CV</link>
    <guid>https://bilbois.me/Unorganised/Mother-CV</guid>
    <description>Victoria Fayers Address: censored Phone: censored Email: censored I have been fortunate enough to gather a wealth of experience working in an educational setting, as well as a challenging ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:20:28 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Goals for Nineteen</title>
    <link>https://bilbois.me/Main-Vibes/Goals-for-Nineteen</link>
    <guid>https://bilbois.me/Main-Vibes/Goals-for-Nineteen</guid>
    <description>todo TODO Convert this brain dump into some actual goals: Chess, Japanese, Retail Job, Tutoring Job, complete all ongoing programming projects, read a full book, establish a consistent ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:06:34 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Cookie Cutter Chat</title>
    <link>https://bilbois.me/Auto-Generated/AI-Chats/Cookie-Cutter-Chat</link>
    <guid>https://bilbois.me/Auto-Generated/AI-Chats/Cookie-Cutter-Chat</guid>
    <description>user: Can you walk me through how and why I’d use cookiecutter in Python? ai: Certainly! Cookiecutter is a command-line utility that creates projects from cookiecutters (project ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 23:07:41 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Main Vibes</title>
    <link>https://bilbois.me/Main-Vibes/Main-Vibes</link>
    <guid>https://bilbois.me/Main-Vibes/Main-Vibes</guid>
    <description>Welcome to my main hub! Below are my essential to-do lists and notes that I use almost every day. Feel free to explore! id: df0e0be4-1968-4a96-a8dc-99d47f227cb8 folderPath: &quot;&quot; title: &quot;{{folderName}}&quot; showTitle: false depth: 10 style: list includeTypes: - folder - markdown disableFileTag: false sortBy: modified sortByAsc: false showEmptyFolders: true onlyIncludeSubfolders: false storeFolderCondition: false showFolderNotes: true disableCollapseIcon: true Note The code block below is a button I use to sync and build my vault notes with Quartz.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:17:03 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>